(Sheldon:)Okay, so the final four forts
(Sheldon:)in the first annual
best fort ever contest,
or "fort off," are...
(Sheldon:)...Fort Knox,
(Sheldon:)Fort Ticonderoga,
(Sheldon:)Fort Sumter and...
(Sheldon:)Fort Cozy McBlanket.
(Leonard:)I'd say...
(Amy:)Knox over Ticonderoga
(Amy:)'cause it's got the gold.
(Sheldon:)Mm-hmm.
And McBlanket over Sumter
(Amy:)'cause it has
a higher thread count.
(phone rings)
Oh.
10:00.
(Amy:)Date night's over.
(Sheldon:)Wait, no.
(Sheldon:)We haven't picked a winner.
(Amy:)We both know
this one's gonna win.
(Sheldon:)Well, of course we do.
(Sheldon:)Fort Knox doesn't have a secret
(Sheldon:)physics lending library.
(Amy:)Come on, I'll help
you take this down.
(Howard:)Well, wait.
(Sheldon:)What if, just this once,
(Sheldon:)we suspend
the date night parameters
(Sheldon:)and you stay later?